question_data = [
{"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In 1993 Swedish car manufacturer Saab experimented with replacing the steering wheel with a joystick in a Saab 9000.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "It was once believed that injecting shark cartilage into people would prevent them from contracting cancer.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "If you could fold a piece of paper in half 50 times, its&#039; thickness will be 3\/4th the distance from the Earth to the Sun.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "&quot;Cube&quot;, &quot;Cube 2: Hypercube&quot; and &quot;Cube Zero&quot; were directed by the same person.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Switzerland has four national languages, English being one of them.",
"correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Harry Potter was born on July 31st, 1980.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Druid is a mage class in &quot;Log Horizon&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing &quot;Spoons&quot; as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The song Scatman&#039;s World was released after Scatman (Ski-Ba-Bop-Ba-Dop-Bop).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
